<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="impossible_game">Impossible Game</string>
    <string name="header_name_app">☆Pro Name Generator☆</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_body_1_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_body_2_material">sans-serif-medium</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_button_material">sans-serif-medium</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_caption_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_1_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_2_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_3_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_4_material">sans-serif-light</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_headline_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_menu_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_subhead_material">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_title_material">sans-serif-medium</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">Alt+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">Ctrl+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">delete</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">enter</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">Function+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">Meta+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">Shift+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">space</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">Sym+</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">Menu+</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="accep_video">Para desbloquear 5 letras premium debes ver el siguiente video hasta el final</string>
    <string name="accept">Aceptar</string>
    <string name="ad_attribution">Ad</string>
    <string name="admob_id">ca-app-pub-3671494685989125~4786818515</string>
    <string name="aleatorio">Aleatorio</string>
    <string name="app_name">Nickname Generator Pro</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="atras">Atras</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancelar</string>
    <string name="character_counter_content_description">Character limit exceeded %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d / %2$d</string>
    <string name="close">Cerrar</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_button">Enable</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_text">%1$s won\'t work unless you enable Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_title">Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_button">Install</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text">%1$s won\'t run without Google Play services, which are missing from your device.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_title">Get Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_channel_name">Google Play services availability</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_ticker">Google Play services error</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_text">%1$s won\'t run without Google Play services, which are not supported by your device.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_button">Update</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_text">%1$s won\'t run unless you update Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_title">Update Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_text">%1$s won\'t run without Google Play services, which are currently updating.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_wear_update_text">New version of Google Play services needed. It will update itself shortly.</string>
    <string name="common_open_on_phone">Open on phone</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">Sign in</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text_long">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="continuar">¿Estas de acuerdo?</string>
    <string name="copiado">¡copiado!</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">155035141546-nrcm5qm0qbuo7oqbtfjtds42rv7p6723.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="des_terminos">Esta política de privacidad rige su uso de la aplicación de software Name Creator (Aplicación) para dispositivos móviles creada por Samuel Sanchez y Martin Rodriguez (Rodriguez &amp; Sanchez). La aplicación es una herramienta creadora de nombres que ayuda a los usuarios a convertir texto normal a diferentes nombres, nombres de usuario y apodos con estilo.\10</string>
    <string name="des_terminos_2">What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?\n\n Information provided by the user\n The Application obtains the information that you provide when you download and register the Application. Registering with us is optional. However, please note that you may not be able to use some of the features offered by the Application unless you register with us.\n When you register with us and use the Application, you generally provide your name, email address, age, username, password, and other registration information; information related to the transaction, such as when you make purchases, respond to any offers or download or use applications from us; © information you provide to us when you contact us for assistance; credit card information for the purchase and use of the Application, and; information you enter into our system when you use the Application, such as contact information and project management information.\n We may also use the information you provided to contact you periodically to provide you with important information, required notices, and marketing promotions.\n\n Information collected automatically\n In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, the unique identification of your mobile device, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile device The Internet browsers you use and information about how you use the Application.\n\n Does the app collect accurate real-time location information from the device?\n This application does not collect accurate information about the location of your mobile device. \n\n Do third parties see and / or have access to the information obtained by the Application?\n Only aggregated anonymous data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Application and our service. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.\n\n We may disclose information provided by the user and collected automatically:\n as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process;\n when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or that of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;\n With our trusted service providers working on our behalf, they have no independent use of the information we disclose to them and have agreed to abide by the rules set forth in this privacy statement.\n si Sanchez &amp; Rodriguez Apps is involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified by email and / or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or use of this information, as well like any choice you may have regarding this information.\n\n What are my exclusion rights?\n You can stop all information collection by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You can use the standard uninstall processes that are available as part of your mobile device or through the marketplace or mobile application network. You can also request exclusion by email, at luxuryapps08@gmail.com\n\n Data retention policy, management of your information\n We will retain the data provided by the user for as long as they use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain the automatically collected information for up to 24 months, and thereafter we may store it together. If you want us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided through the Application, please contact us at luxuryapps08@gmail.com and we will respond to you in a reasonable time.\n Please note that some or all of the data provided by the user may be necessary for the application to function properly.\n\n Children\n We do not use the App to knowingly solicit information or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that their child has provided us with information without their consent, they should contact us at elimoretabs@gmail.com. We will remove such information from our files within a reasonable time.\n\n Security\n We are concerned with safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information to operate, develop, or improve our Application. Please note that while we strive to provide reasonable security for the information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all possible security breaches.\n\n Changes\n This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here and will inform you by email or text message. It is recommended that you check this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is considered approval of all changes. You can check the history of this policy by clicking here. \n\n Your Consent \ nBy using the Application, you agree that we process your information as set out in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. Processing means using cookies on a computer / handheld device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all activities that will take place in the United States . If you reside outside of the United States, your information will be transferred, processed, and stored there under United States privacy standards.\n\n Contact \ n If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us by email at luxuryapps08@gmail.com </string>
    <string name="desc_text">Puedes pegarlo o compartirlo en cualquier app</string>
    <string name="dialog_positive_button">¡Si Quiero!</string>
    <string name="dialog_positive_desc">¿Te gustaría dejar tu opinión en la Play Store? Eso nos motiva mucho a seguir mejorando esta APP.</string>
    <string name="disponible">disponibles</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_scrim_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationScrimBehavior</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="fcm_fallback_notification_channel_label">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="firebase_database_url">https://nicksname-64c97.firebaseio.com</string>
    <string name="fontns_ok">+5 fuentes disponibles</string>
    <string name="full_fonts">Styles unlocked!!</string>
    <string name="gcm_defaultSenderId">155035141546</string>
    <string name="google_api_key">AIzaSyDcw9Qqb_XP3wKC664gw_iYpJUQl23KNWU</string>
    <string name="google_app_id">1:155035141546:android:6b948a6c0c49d87b</string>
    <string name="google_crash_reporting_api_key">AIzaSyDcw9Qqb_XP3wKC664gw_iYpJUQl23KNWU</string>
    <string name="google_storage_bucket">nicksname-64c97.appspot.com</string>
    <string name="hide_bottom_view_on_scroll_behavior">com.google.android.material.behavior.HideBottomViewOnScrollBehavior</string>
    <string name="intersticial">ca-app-pub-3671494685989125/7221410162</string>
    <string name="location_not_available_message">Looks like this app doesn\'t have location services configured. Please see OneSignal docs for more information.</string>
    <string name="location_not_available_open_settings_message">You have previously denied sharing your device location. Please go to settings to enable.</string>
    <string name="location_not_available_open_settings_option">Settings</string>
    <string name="location_not_available_title">Location Not Available</string>
    <string name="mtrl_chip_close_icon_content_description">Remove %1$s</string>
    <string name="native_id">ca-app-pub-3671494685989125/424543762</string>
    <string name="negative_title_rate_app">¡Lo sentimos mucho!</string>
    <string name="not_conettion">No tienes conexion a internet</string>
    <string name="not_copy">No hay favoritos</string>
    <string name="number_cero">0</string>
    <string name="obtener">desbloquear 5 estilos de</string>
    <string name="password_toggle_content_description">Show password</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye">M12,4.5C7,4.5 2.73,7.61 1,12c1.73,4.39 6,7.5 11,7.5s9.27,-3.11 11,-7.5c-1.73,-4.39 -6,-7.5 -11,-7.5zM12,17c-2.76,0 -5,-2.24 -5,-5s2.24,-5 5,-5 5,2.24 5,5 -2.24,5 -5,5zM12,9c-1.66,0 -3,1.34 -3,3s1.34,3 3,3 3,-1.34 3,-3 -1.34,-3 -3,-3z</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye_mask_strike_through">M2,4.27 L19.73,22 L22.27,19.46 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1 L23,1 L23,23 L1,23 L1,4.27 Z</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye_mask_visible">M2,4.27 L2,4.27 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1 L23,1 L23,23 L1,23 L1,4.27 Z</string>
    <string name="path_password_strike_through">M3.27,4.27 L19.74,20.74</string>
    <string name="project_id">nicksname-64c97</string>
    <string name="question_one">Te gusta la app?</string>
    <string name="question_two">Te invitó a que me dejes tu calificación en la playstore</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Calificanos</string>
    <string name="s1">Save image</string>
    <string name="s2">Allow Ad to store image in Picture gallery?</string>
    <string name="s3">Accept</string>
    <string name="s4">Decline</string>
    <string name="s5">Create calendar event</string>
    <string name="s6">Allow Ad to create a calendar event?</string>
    <string name="s7">Test Ad</string>
    <string name="save_nick">Copiados y Guardados:</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">Search</string>
    <string name="share_app">Compartir App</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="terminos">Politicas de privacidad</string>
    <string name="thanks_b_negative_rate_app">Enviar</string>
    <string name="thanks_b_positive_rate_app">No, gracias</string>
    <string name="thanks_description_rate_app">¿Que experiencia negativo tuvo con esta aplicación? Su opinión es importante para mejorar esta app.</string>
    <string name="thanks_title_rate_app">¡Gracias!</string>
    <string name="titleApp">Generador De Nombres Pro</string>
    <string name="title_rate_app">¿Que puntaje le das a esta aplicación?</string>
    <string name="unexpected">Error inesperado, Intentalo mas tarde</string>
    <string name="wait">Espere un momento</string>
    <string name="copy_text">★Name Generator Pro★</string>
    <string name="copied">COPIED</string>
    <string name="cancopy">You can paste or share it in any app</string>
    <string name="text_close">CLOSE</string>
</resources>
